[{"question": "Which of the following activation functions would always result in the model extrapolating to zero for features greater than the training data in value?", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Radial Basis Function", "correct": false}, {"answer": "tanh", "correct": false}, {"answer": "RelU", "correct": false}, {"answer": "None of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "activation_function", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "RelU(-10) would give the output", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "10", "correct": false}, {"answer": "-10", "correct": false}, {"answer": "0", "correct": true}, {"answer": "100", "correct": false}], "tag": "activation_function", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "A neural network with a constant value multiplier as the activation function, will give us a model which is equivalent to", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Non-linear regression", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Linear regression", "correct": true}, {"answer": "A neural network with a tanh activation", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A neural network with a RelU activation", "correct": false}], "tag": "activation_function", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "The number of neurons in the first layer of a neural network should be", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Less than or equal to the number of input variables", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Greater than or equal to the number of input variables", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Always equal to the number of input variables", "correct": false}, {"answer": "There is no set rule and depends on the problem at hand", "correct": true}], "tag": "neural_network", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "Neural networks can be used for", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Classification", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Regression", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Feature Engineering", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "neural_network", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "For a finite data set and a single layer neural network with a tanh activation function, a data point at -inf would give the output as", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "-inf", "correct": false}, {"answer": "+inf", "correct": false}, {"answer": "a finite value", "correct": true}, {"answer": "-1", "correct": false}], "tag": "activation_function", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "If the training error is 0, then it is most likely that", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "We have a perfect model generalising the data", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The model is overfitting", "correct": true}, {"answer": "The model is underfitting", "correct": false}, {"answer": "The model is non-linear", "correct": false}], "tag": "train_test", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "A good model will most probably have", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Test error slighlty higher than the training error", "correct": true}, {"answer": "Test error much higher than the training error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Test error equal to the training error", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Test error much lower than the training error", "correct": false}], "tag": "train_test", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "As the number of epochs in training a neural network would increase, assuming the model converges eventually, the training error would", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Keep on increasing", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Keep on decreasing", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Decrease then increase", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Decrease and will reach a constant value", "correct": true}], "tag": "train_test epoch", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}, {"question": "Reducing the step size will result in", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "No changes in the model performance", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Less epochs required to reach the desired accuracy", "correct": false}, {"answer": "More epochs required to reach the desired accuracy", "correct": true}, {"answer": "A smaller neural network", "correct": false}], "tag": "neural_network step_size epoch", "lecture_file": "22_ml_2"}]